A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential records, Advance Office, Series 1 FA781
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential records, Advance Office, Series 1
1975-1977
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
United States. Office of the Vice President.
FA781
8.23 Cubic Feet 17 legal document boxes, 1 half legal document box.
Scope and Contents
Types of records include: correspondence, travel logs, brochures and pamphlets, photographs, newspaper articles, and guest lists.
Arrangement
These records are in two subseries, 1-Events and 2-Vice Presidential Staff Correspondence.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for scholarly research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Other Finding Aids
Detailed finding aids for each series of this collection are available:
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Richard Allison (FA377)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Central Files (FA378)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, National Commission on Water Quality (FA379)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, New York Office (FA380)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Joseph E. Persico (FA381)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Press Releases (FA382)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Speeches (FA383)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Working Papers of the Vice President (FA384)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Foreign Affairs and National Security (FA385)
- Events, 1975-1976; 1
  Scope and Contents
  Nelson A. Rockefeller's itinerary as Vice President of the United States during the years 1975-1976
  - Original Box Inventories, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Sultan of Oman Lunch, Anderson House, Washington, DC, 1975 January 10 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Republican Congregational Campaign Committee, Washington, DC, 1975 January 22 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Business Leadership Conference, Chicago, IL, 1975 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Business Leadership Conference, Chicago, IL, 1975 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 4A)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted from scholarly access-Confidential material
  - Washington Press Club Salute to Congress, Washington, D. C., 1975 January 28 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - National Prayer Breakfast, Washington, D. C., 1975 January 30 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GOP Fundraising Dinner, Milburn, NJ, 1975 January 30, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - GOP Fundraising Dinner, Milburn, NJ, 1975 January 30, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 7A)
  - New Jersey, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Department of Tourism Lunch, Washington, D. C., 1975 February 4 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Senate Youth Program, Pine Crest Students, Washington, D. C., 1975 February 5 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Honor the Vice President Dinner, NY, NY, 1975 February 13 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Governors Club Dinner, NY, NY, 1975 February 14 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - United States Chamber of Commerce, American Society of Association Executives, Washington, D. C., 1975 February 19 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The World Wildlife Fund Reception, Washington, D. C., 1975 February 19 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - National Governors Conference, Washington, D. C., 1975 February 19 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Chowder & Marching Society Breakfast, Washington, D. C., 1975 February 26 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Society of Automotive Executives Convention Dinner, Detroit, MI, 1975 February 26 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - South Carolina Delegation to Young Republican Leadership Conference, Washington, D. C., 1975 February 26 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - National Conference of Christians & Jews, Washington, D. C., 1975 March 4 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - NBC (National Broadcasting Company) Reception, Washington, D. C., 1975 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Republican Leadership Conference Lunch, Washington, D. C., 1975 March 7 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Republican Leadership Conference Lunch, Washington, D. C., 1975 March 7 (Box 1, Folder 21A)
  - The Gridiron Club Dinner, Washington, D. C., 1975 March 22 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Saudi Arabia, 1975 March 25-27 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Buffalo, NY, 1975 April 2 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Buffalo, NY, 1975 April 2 (Box 1, Folder 24A)
  - Outstanding Handicapped Federal Employees, Washington, D. C., 1975 April 3 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Interdepartmental Savings Bonds Committee, Washington, D. C., 1975 April 9 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - New Orleans, LA, 1975 April 9 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - The President's Commission on Personal Interchange, Washington, D.C., 1975 April 10 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - National Commission for International Women's Year, Washington, D. C., 1975 April 10 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Joint Session of Congress, U. S. Capitol, Washington, D. C., 1975 April 10 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - National Association of Manufacturers, Washington, D. C., 1975 April 11 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Republican House Senate Dinner, Washington, D. C., 1975 April 15 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - White House News Photographers Association Dinner, Washington, D. C., 1975 April 16 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - The Young Presidents' Organization, Boca Raton, FL, 1975 April 18 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - The Advertising Council Lunch, Washington, D. C., 1975 April 23 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - National Academy of Engineering Reception, Washington, D. C., 1975 April 23 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - National Volunteer Awards, Washington, D. C., 1975 April 24 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - National Volunteer Awards, Washington, D. C., 1975 April 24 (Box 2, Folder 37A)
  - Library of Congress Bicentennial Opening, Washington, D. C., 1975 April 24 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - New York State Senate Campaign Committee, New York, NY, 1975 April 27 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States, Washington, D. C., 1975 April 29 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Garden Club of America, Washington, D. C., 1975 April 29 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - National Urban Coalition, Washington, D. C., 1975 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - The White House Correspondents Association, Washington, D. C., 1975 May 3 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Institutional Investor Institute, Washington, D. C., 1975 May 6 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - The Capitol Hill Club, Washington, D. C., 1975 May 6 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - The Business Council, Hot Springs, VA, 1975 May 9 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - The Federal City Council, Washington, D. C., 1975 May 12 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Museum of Modern Art, New York, NY, 1975 May 13 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Congressman Jack Wydler of New York, Washington, D. C., 1975 May 14 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Congressman Jack Wydler of New York, Washington, D. C., 1975 May 14 (Box 2, Folder 49A)
  - Republican Heritage Groups, Washington, D. C., 1975 May 16 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - The Securities Industry Association, New York, NY, 1975 May 19 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Congressional Black Caucus, Washington, D., C., 1975 May 20 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - The Bull Elephants, Washington, D. C., 1975 May 21 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Galo Plaza Dinner, Washington, D. C., 1975 May 21 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Supreme Court Chamber Opening, Washington, D.C., 1975 May 22 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Motion Picture Association Reception, Washington, D. C., 1975 June 2 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - New York Stock Exchange, Washington, D. C., 1975 June 4 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Naval Academy Graduation, Annapolis, MD, 1975 June 4 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Sigma Delta Chi, Washington, D. C., 1975 June 6 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - MFR Potomac River/Mt. Vernon Cruise, 1975 June 11 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - New York Republican State Dinner Committee, New York, NY, 1975 June 12 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Wolf Trap park, Vienna, VA, 1975 June 23 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - O.A.S./Galo Plaza Dinner, Washington, D. C., 1975 June 24 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Atlanta, GA, 1975 July 9 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Victor Borella Funeral, Hanover, NH, 1975 July 12 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Water Quality Commission Picnic, Washington, D. C., 1975 July 15 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Water Quality Commission Picnic, Washington, D. C., 1975 July 15 (Box 3, Folder 66A)
  - Vice Presidential Staff Picnic, Washington, D. C., 1975 July 17 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Midwest Governor's Conference, Cincinnati, OH, 1975 July 22 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Vice Presidential Press Picnic, Washington, D. C., 1975 July 23 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Productivity Commission, Pittsburgh, PA, 1975 July 25 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Congress of the World Federation of Deaf, Washington, D. C., 1975 August 5 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Maine Republican State Committee Fundraising Reception, Seal Harbor, ME, 1975 August 22 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Moreland Commission, Buffalo/Warsaw, NY, 1975 August 29 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - National Lt. Governor's Conference, Mobile, AL, 1975 August 26-27 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Republican Leadership Conference, Columbia, SC, 1975 August 26, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Republican Leadership Conference, Columbia, SC, 1975 August 26, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 75A)
  - Savings Bond Luncheon, Rochester, NY & Park Ridge Hospital Dedication, Greece, NY, 1975 September 5, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Capitol Hill Club Fundraising Reception, Washington, D. C., 1975 September 10 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Savings Bond Award Ceremony, Washington, D. C., 1975 September 10 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - National Federation Republican Women Convention, Dallas, TX & Oklahoma Events, Norman and Enid, 1975 September 12-13 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - National Federation Republican Women Convention, Dallas, TX & Oklahoma Events, Norman and Enid, 1975 September 12-13 (Box 4, Folder 79A)
  - Oklahoma/Oregon Football Game, Etc., Norman, OK, 1975 September 13, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Presidential Delegation to the Opening of "The World of Franklin and Jefferson" Exhibition, London, England, 1975 September 15 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Reading is Fundamental, Washington, D. C., 1975 September 17 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Reading is Fundamental, Washington, D. C., 1975 September 17 (Box 4, Folder 82A)
  - National Science Foundation, Washington, D. C., 1975 September 17 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Senate Staff Picnic, Washington, D. C., 1975 September 18 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Congressional Golf Tournament, Washington, D. C., 1975 September 22 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Federal City Council, Washington, D. C., 1975 September 29 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Board of Regents Meeting and Dinner, Washington, D. C., 1975 September 30 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Evans and Novack Political Forum, Washington, D. C., 1975 October 1 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - The National Energy Project Conference, Washington, D.C., 1975 October 2 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Western States Republican Conference, Portland, OR, 1975 October 3, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Western States Republican Conference, Portland, OR, 1975 October 3, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 90A)
  - Bicentennial Parade, Kings Mountain, NC, 1975 October 7, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Change Magazine Award Luncheon, Washington. D. C., 1975 October 7 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Christening Dwight D. Einsenhower, Newport News, VA, 1975 October 11 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Annual Columbus Day Dinner, New York, NY, 1975 October 11 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - GOP Leadership Meeting and Dinner, Columbus, OH, 1975 October 15, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - GOP Fundraising Reception and Dinner, Charleston, WV, 1975 October 16 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Roanoke, VA, 1975 October 16, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Society of American Travel Writers Awards Luncheon, Washington, D. C., 1975 October 17 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - White House Public Forums, Denver, CO, 1975 October 21-22 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - United Fund Kick-Off Drive, Indianapolis, IN, 1975 October 23, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - United Fund Kick-Off Drive, Indianapolis, IN, 1975 October 23, Publications (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - Indiana State Republican Committee, Indianapolis, IN, 1975 October 23 (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - Congressman John Anderson Fundraising Party, Washington, D. C., 1975 October 23 (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - Republican Reception, Decatur, IL, 1975 October 23 (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - United Negro College Fund Reception, Milwaukee, WI, 1975 October 24 (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - United Negro College Fund Reception, Milwaukee, WI, 1975 October 24 (Box 6, Folder 105A)
  - President Sadat Visit to U. S., Washington, D. C./Pocantico, NY, 1975 October 27-29 (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - Public Forum on Domestic Policy IV, Tampa/St. Petersburg, FL, 1975 October 29 (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - Hebrew Union College Centennial Convocation, New York, NY, 1975 October 30 (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - United States Chamber of Commerce, Washington, D. C., 1975 November 5 (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - Public forum on Domestic Policy VI, Austin, TX, 1975 November 11, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - Reception for Larry Spivak, NBC, Washington, D. C., 1975 November 11 (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - Daniel Boorsin Swearing In at the Library of Congress, Washington, D. C., 1975 November 12 (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - Future Farmers of America Convention, Kansas City, MO, 1975 November 14 (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - McClory Dinner, Lincolnshire, IL, 1975 November 14 (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - Minnesota Republican State Convention, St. Paul, MN, 1975 November 15, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Public Forum on Domestic Policy III, Philadelphia, PA, 1975 November 18 (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Council of 100, Washington, D. C., 1975 November 19 (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Republican Governors Conference, Wichita, KS, 1975 November 20-21, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - The State Funeral of President Franco of Spain, Madrid, 1975 November 21-27 (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Public Forum on Domestic Policy, Indianapolis, IN, 1975 November 25 (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - 25th Annual Inaugural Dinner, United Jewish Appeal (UJA)/Federation Fundraising Campaign, New York, NY, 1975 November 25 (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - New York State Republican Dinner, New York, NY, 1975 December 2 (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Distinguished Republican Award Dinner, Pittsburgh, PA. 1975 December 4, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Distinguished Republican Award Dinner, Pittsburgh, PA. 1975 December 4, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 123A)
  - National Association of Manufacturers Dinner, New York, NY, 1975 December 5 (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - White House Public Forum, Los Angeles, CA, 1975 December 8-9, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - Republican Boosters Reception, Walt Disney's World Showcase, & Council on Environmental Quality Luncheon, Washington, D. C., 1975 December 10 (Box 8, Folder 126)
  - Metro Center Luncheon, Nashville, TN, 1975 December 11, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 127)
  - Southern States Republican Conference, Houston, TX, 1975 December 11-12, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 128)
  - President's Safety Award Ceremony, Washington, D. C., 1975 December 17 (Box 8, Folder 129)
  - President's Safety Award Ceremony, Washington, D. C., 1975 December 17 (Box 8, Folder 129A)
  - Time Magazine Editors' Luncheon, Washington, D. C., 1976 January 12 (Box 8, Folder 130)
  - National Council of Farmers Cooperatives, Washington, D. C., 1976 January 14 (Box 8, Folder 131)
  - National Council of Farmers Cooperatives, Washington, D. C., 1976 January 14 (Box 8, Folder 131A)
  - State of the Union Message, Washington, D. C., 1976 January 19 (Box 8, Folder 132)
  - Salem College Convocation, Salem, WV, 1976 January 26 (Box 8, Folder 133)
  - Salem College Convocation, Salem, WV, 1976 January 26 (Box 8, Folder 133A)
  - Service Wives' Clubs Address, Bolling Air Force Base, Washington, D. C., 1976 January 26 (Box 8, Folder 134)
  - Salute to the President, New York, NY, 1976 January 28 (Box 8, Folder 135)
  - Westchester County Republican Dinner, Rye, NY, 1975 January 29, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 136)
  - Midwest Republican Conference, Dearborn, MI, 1976 January 30 (Box 8, Folder 137)
  - Government Operations Committee Hearings, Our Third World Century: Direction, Washington, D. C., 1976 February 4 (Box 8, Folder 138)
  - William Randolph Hearst Foundation, Washington, D. C., 1976 February 4, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 139)
  - Northeast Republican Conference, Washington, D. C., 1976 February 6 (Box 8, Folder 140)
  - Atomic Industrial Forum, Inc., Washington, D. C., 1976 February 10 (Box 8, Folder 141)
  - Labor Leadership Meeting & Dinner, Miami, FL, 1976 February 11-12 (Box 8, Folder 142)
  - Lincoln Day Dinner, Louisville, KY, 1976 February 12 (Box 8, Folder 143)
  - Fundraising Luncheon, Lexington, KY, 1976 February 12 (Box 8, Folder 144)
  - Governor's Club Dinner, New York, NY, 1976 February 13 (Box 9, Folder 145)
  - New York County Dinner, New York, NY, 1976 February 14 (Box 9, Folder 146)
  - National Press Club Luncheon, Washington, D. C., 1976 February 18 (Box 9, Folder 147)
  - Lincoln Day Dinner, Lansing, MI, 1976 February 20 (Box 9, Folder 148)
  - Lincoln Day Dinner, Lansing, MI, 1976 February 20 (Box 9, Folder 148A)
  - American Association for Advancement of Science, Boston, MA, 1976 February 23 (Box 9, Folder 149)
  - American Association for Advancement of Science, Boston, MA, 1976 February 23 (Box 9, Folder 149A)
  - Bicentennial Bishop Celebration, Philadelphia, PA, 1976 February 25 (Box 9, Folder 150)
  - Swearing in of Arthur Fletcher, Deputy Assistant to the President for Urban Affairs, Washington, D. C., 1976 February 26 (Box 9, Folder 151)
  - Swearing in of Arthur Fletcher, Deputy Assistant to the President for Urban Affairs, Washington, D. C., 1976 February 25 (Box 9, Folder 151A)
  - Republican National Committee Reception, Washington, D. C., 1976 February 27 (Box 9, Folder 152)
  - Republican National Committee Reception, Washington, D. C., 1976 February 27 (Box 9, Folder 152A)
  - Religion in American Life Dinner, New York, NY, 1976 March 9 (Box 9, Folder 153)
  - National Industrial Energy Council, Commerce Department, Washington, D. C., 1976 March 10 (Box 9, Folder 154)
  - Lincoln Day Dinner, Albuquerque, NM, 1976 March 12 (Box 9, Folder 155)
  - American Whole Salers Association, Chicago, IL, 1976 March 16 (Box 9, Folder 156)
  - Dinner with the Prime Minister of Ireland, Liam Cosgrave, Washington, D. C., 1976 March 18 (Box 9, Folder 157)
  - Trip Around the World, 1976 March-April (Box 9, Folder 158)
  - Trip Around the World, 1976 March 20-April 5 (Box 10, Folder 159)
  - Trip Around the World, 1976 March 20-April 5 (Box 10, Folder 160)
  - Dedication of the LBJ Grove, Arlington, VA, 1976 April 6 (Box 10, Folder 161)
  - Americans for Energy Indenpendence, Reston, VA, 1976 April 7 (Box 10, Folder 162)
  - Philadelphia trip, Club of Rome Dinner, Philadelphia, PA, 1976 April 12 (Box 10, Folder 163)
  - The Vice President's Trip to Iowa, Des Moines, IA, 1975 April 14 (Box 10, Folder 164)
  - President's Committee on Personal Interchange, Washington, D. C., 1976 April 20 (Box 10, Folder 165)
  - White House News Photographers Dinner, Washington, D. C., 1976 April 22 (Box 10, Folder 166)
  - American Oceanic Organization Award Dinner, Washington, D. C., 1976 April 28 (Box 11, Folder 167)
  - George Washington Inauguration, Washington, D. C., 1976 April 30 (Box 11, Folder 168)
  - White House Correspondents Dinner, Washington, D. C., 1976 May 1 (Box 11, Folder 169)
  - Commonwealth Club, World Affairs Council, San Francisco & Los Angeles, CA, 1976 May 3-5 (Box 11, Folder 170)
  - Commonwealth Club, World Affairs Council, San Francisco & Los Angeles, CA, 1976 May 3-5 (Box 11, Folder 170A)
  - United Board of Higher Education in Asia Dinner, New York, NY, 1976 May 6 (Box 11, Folder 171)
  - Queens Republican Dinner, Queens, NY, 1976 May 6 (Box 11, Folder 172)
  - President Ford Committee Reception, Westport, CT, 1976 May 7 (Box 11, Folder 173)
  - 10th Anniversary of the Performing Arts, New York Public Library, New York, NY, 1976 May 9 (Box 11, Folder 174)
  - International Press Institute, Philadelphia, PA, 1976 May 10 (Box 11, Folder 175)
  - Accion International Dinner, Center for Inter-American Relations, New York, NY, 1976 May 11 (Box 11, Folder 176)
  - The Vice President's Visit to Frankfurt & Berlin, Germany, 1976 May 13-15 (Box 11, Folder 177)
  - Germany Trip, 1976 May-June (Box 11, Folder 178)
  - Visit of President Giscard d'Estaing, Yorktown, VA, 1976 May 19 (Box 11, Folder 179)
  - President Ford Committee Reception Dinner, Cincinnati, OH, 1976 May 20 (Box 11, Folder 180)
  - 50th Anniversary of the Synagogue, Touro Synagogue, Newport, RI, 1976 May 23 (Box 11, Folder 181)
  - New York Delegate Meeting, Albany, NY, 1976 May 24 (Box 11, Folder 182)
  - Senate Wives Luncheon, MFR, Washington, D. C., 1976 May 25 (Box 11, Folder 183)
  - Dinner-Dance for the Vice President, Chevy Chase, MD, 1976 May 25 (Box 12, Folder 184)
  - San Francisco Chamber Luncheon, Washington, D. C., 1976 May 26 (Box 12, Folder 185)
  - Conference on Regulatory Reform, Washington, D. C., 1976 May 26 (Box 12, Folder 186)
  - U. S. Air Force Academy Graduation Ceremony, Colorado Springs, CO, 1976 June 2 (Box 12, Folder 187)
  - Maryland Campaign Day, Ocean City, MD, 1976 June 4 (Box 12, Folder 188)
  - President Ford Committee Fundraising Reception, Washington, D. C., 1976 June 8 (Box 12, Folder 190)
  - National Broadcast Editors Association, Washington, D. C., 1976 June 9 (Box 12, Folder 191)
  - Interamerican Defense College, Fort McNair, Washington, D. C., 1976 June 10 (Box 12, Folder 192)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, New York, NY, 1976 June 10 (Box 12, Folder 193)
  - Dedication of Old Senate Chamber, Washington, D. C., 1976 June 16 (Box 12, Folder 194)
  - National Housing Dinner, Washington, D. C., 1976 June 16 (Box 12, Folder 195)
  - New York State Republican Dinner, New York, NY, 1976 June 17 (Box 12, Folder 196)
  - Republican State Convention, Greensboro, NC, 1976 June 18 (Box 12, Folder 197)
  - Republican Finance Reception, Livingston & West Orange, NJ, 1976 June 21 (Box 12, Folder 198)
  - American Friends of Hebrew University, Washington, D. C., 1976 June 22 (Box 12, Folder 199)
  - CIA Visit, Langley, VA, 1976 June 22 (Box 12, Folder 200)
  - American Folk Life Festival, Washington, D. C., 1976 June 23 (Box 12, Folder 201)
  - Nassau County Republican Dinner, Hauppauge, NY, 1976 June 24 (Box 12, Folder 202)
  - Tunisian Mosaic Opening Ceremony, Washington, D. C., 1976 June 29 (Box 12, Folder 203)
  - Reception for Senator J. Glenn Beall, Washington, D. C., 1976 June 29 (Box 12, Folder 204)
  - Prime Minister Miki Reception, Embassy of Japan, Washington, D. C., 1976 June 29 (Box 12, Folder 205)
  - 1976 Estes Kefauver Award Luncheon, Washington, D. C., 1976 June 30 (Box 12, Folder 206)
  - Air and Space Museum Opening, The Smithsonian, Washington, D. C., 1976 July 1 (Box 12, Folder 207)
  - Census Bureau/Univac Ceremony, Suitland, MD, 1976 July 1 (Box 13, Folder 208)
  - Marine Barracks & Parade, Washington, D. C., 1976 July 2 (Box 13, Folder 209)
  - National Archives Bicentennial, Washington, D. C., 1976 July 2 (Box 13, Folder 210)
  - Happy Birthday USA Parade, Washington, D. C., 1976 July 3 (Box 13, Folder 211)
  - Fourth of July Celebration-1976, Washington, D. C., 1976 July 4 (Box 13, Folder 212)
  - "Operation Sail", New York, NY, 1976 July 4 (Box 13, Folder 213)
  - Pageant of Freedom, Fireworks, Washington, D. C., 1976 July 4 (Box 13, Folder 214)
  - Her Majesty, Elizabeth II's Visit, Washington D. C. & Rhode Island, 1976 July 7-10 (Box 13, Folder 215)
  - Saudi Arabian Luncheon, Washington, D. C., 1976 July 9 (Box 13, Folder 216)
  - Visit of Chancellor Schmidt, Air and Space Museum Ceremony, Washington, D. C., 1976 July 15 (Box 13, Folder 217)
  - Delaware State GOP Dinner, Wilmington, DE, 1976 July 19 (Box 13, Folder 218)
  - Danzansky Dinner Party, Happy Birthday USA, Washington, D. C., 1976 July 20 (Box 13, Folder 219)
  - Republican National Hispanic Assembly Reception, Washington, D. C., 1976 July 29 (Box 13, Folder 220)
  - Maine State Republican Day, Seal Harbor, ME, 1976 August 2 (Box 13, Folder 221)